Guide to the Pittsburgh Playhouse School of the Theater Records, 1934-1994 CTC.1981.01
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Photographs and Negatives, 1935-1993; III.
  - Individual Performers' Photographs, 1.
    - Walter, John (Box 77, Folder 104)
    - Wandres, Anne (Box 77, Folder 105)
    - Ward, Audrey (Box 77, Folder 106)
    - Ward, Madelyn (Box 77, Folder 107)
    - Warlock, David (Box 77, Folder 108)
    - Wallace, Lee (Box 78, Folder 1)
    - Walker, Jewel (Box 78, Folder 2)
    - Walson, Don (Box 78, Folder 3)
    - Warlock, Robert Winifred E. (Box 78, Folder 4)
    - Washington, Althea (Box 78, Folder 5)
    - Webster, Kenneth (Box 78, Folder 6)
    - Webster, Margaret (Box 78, Folder 7)
    - Weddle, Vernon (Box 78, Folder 8)
    - Weems, Jim (Box 78, Folder 9)
    - Weil, Ferninand (Box 78, Folder 10)
    - Wells, Jennifer (Box 78, Folder 11)
    - Wells, Mary Jane (Box 78, Folder 12)
    - Weltz, David (Box 78, Folder 13)
    - West, Clara (Box 78, Folder 14)
    - Whitman, Dale (Box 78, Folder 15)
    - Wible, Nancy (Box 78, Folder 16)
    - Wikander, Rosiland (Box 78, Folder 17)
    - Wilder, Ian (Box 78, Folder 18)
    - Wilkinson, Edward (Box 78, Folder 19)
    - Wilkinson, Kate (Box 78, Folder 20)
    - Williams, Edmund (Box 78, Folder 21)
    - Williams, Jennifer (Box 78, Folder 22)
    - Willoughby, Ronald (Box 78, Folder 23)
    - Wilmot, Tom (Box 78, Folder 24)
    - Wipf, Alex (Box 78, Folder 25)
    - Wither, Nan (Box 78, Folder 26)
    - Witt, Howard (Box 78, Folder 27)
    - Wolfe, Catherine (Box 78, Folder 28)
    - Wolk, Leonore (Box 78, Folder 29)
    - Wood, G. and Welch, K. (Box 78, Folder 30)
    - Wood, Lynn (Box 78, Folder 31)
    - Wood, Mary Laura (Box 78, Folder 32)
    - Wood, Susan (Box 78, Folder 33)
    - Woodburn, Arthur (Box 78, Folder 34)
    - Woodman, William (Box 78, Folder 35)
    - Woolman, Claude (Box 78, Folder 36)
    - Woodworth, Ed (Box 78, Folder 37)
    - Worth, Alice (Box 78, Folder 38)
    - Wyler, Bruce (Box 78, Folder 39)
    - Wyman, Stephen (Box 78, Folder 40)
    - Wynkoap, Christopher (Box 78, Folder 41)
    - Yates, Sterling (Box 78, Folder 42)
    - Young, Edward (Box 78, Folder 43)
    - Young, Herbert (Box 78, Folder 44)
    - Young, Janice (Box 78, Folder 45)
    - Young, William (Box 78, Folder 46)
    - Youngling, Mary Lou (Box 78, Folder 47)
    - Yulin, Harris (Box 78, Folder 48)
    - Zulick, Steve (Box 78, Folder 49)
    - Family Portraits - Unidentified (Box 78, Folder 50)
    - Portraits - Unidentified female (Box 78, Folder 51-52)
    - Portraits - Unidentified male (Box 78, Folder 53-54)
    - Costume Shop - Women sewing and constructing costumes (Box 78, Folder 55)
    - School - Classroom and backstage (Box 78, Folder 56)
    - A.C.T. at the Playhouse - Opening night and party (Box 78, Folder 57)
    - Playhouse building exterior (Box 79, Folder 1)
    - Playhouse Jr. - Miscellaneous unidentified productions (Box 79, Folder 2)
    - Lillian Russell Room (Box 79, Folder 3)
    - Restaurant and Bar (Box 79, Folder 4-5)
    - Salesman [Film] (Box 79, Folder 6)
    - Save the Playhouse Campaign (Box 79, Folder 7)
    - School Dance Department (Box 79, Folder 8)
    - School Registration (Box 79, Folder 9)
    - School Scholarship (Box 79, Folder 10)
    - School - Miscellaneous unidentified productions (Box 79, Folder 11)
    - School - TV Productions (Box 79, Folder 12)
    - School students - Unidentified (Box 79, Folder 13)
    - Social Functions (Box 79, Folder 14)
    - Backstage - Miscellaneous technical (Box 79, Folder 15)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 79, Folder 16)
    - TvAR presentation, May 20, 1959 (Box 79, Folder 17)
    - Hospital Visits (Box 79, Folder 18)
    - Miscellaneous contact sheets (Box 79, Folder 19)
    - A.C.T. Steel tour (Box 80, Folder 1)
    - After Hours - Burleigh, Charles Gaynory and others in group photos pertaining to production? (Box 80, Folder 2)
    - Audiences (Box 80, Folder 3)
    - Paintings exhibited at the Playhouse (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - Board of Directors (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - Burleigh Night (Box 80, Folder 6)
    - Burleigh Readings (Box 80, Folder 7)
    - Children's Theater - Backstage and parties (Box 80, Folder 8-9)
    - Civic Nights, 1949-1950 (Box 80, Folder 10)
    - Joan of Lorraine Tour to Midland PA (Box 80, Folder 11)
    - Opening Night of Oklahoma! - With Shirley Jones (Box 80, Folder 12)
    - Offices and Staff (Box 80, Folder 13)
    - On Tour [Joan of Lorraine?] (Box 80, Folder 14)
    - National Shakespeare Company Much Ado About Nothing (Box 80, Folder 15)
    - National Theater of the Deaf (Box 80, Folder 16)
    - Opening Night Gala [Great Sebastians?] (Box 80, Folder 17)
    - Opening Night - Wonderful Good, May 1952 (Box 80, Folder 18)
    - Playhouse Expansion (Box 80, Folder 19)
    - Promotions (Box 80, Folder 20)
    - Promotion and Publicity (Box 80, Folder 21)
    - Promotion - Streetcar (Box 80, Folder 22)
    - Publicity - Displays (Box 80, Folder 23)
    - Publicity - Duel Shots (Box 80, Folder 24)
    - Playhouse Car (Box 80, Folder 25)
  - Production Photographs, 1935-1993; 2.
    Arranged alphabetically by production title unless otherwise specified. There is a small amount of oversize photographs at the end of this subseries.
    - Absent Friends, 1979 (Box 81, Folder 1)
    - Accounting for Love, 1955 (Box 81, Folder 2)
    - An Act Without Words (Box 81, Folder 3)
    - Accent on Youth, 1958 (Box 81, Folder 4)
    - Adventures of the Puppet Prince, 1961 (Box 81, Folder 5)
    - Affairs of State, 1953 (Box 81, Folder 6)
    - After Hours, 1947 (Box 81, Folder 7)
    - After the Fall, 1967 (Box 81, Folder 8)
    - Ah, Wilderness!, 1952 (Box 81, Folder 9)
    - Aladdin and His Magic Lamp, 1964 (Box 81, Folder 10)
    - Aladdin and His Wonderful Lamp, 1955-56 (Box 81, Folder 11-12)
    - Aladdin, 1968? (Box 81, Folder 13)
    - Anything Goes, 198? (Box 81, Folder 14)
    - Ali Baba and the Magic Cave, 1965 (Box 81, Folder 15)
    - Ali Baba and the 40 Thieves, 1956 (Box 81, Folder 16)
    - Alice in Wonderland, 1963 (Box 81, Folder 17)
    - Alfred the Great, 1971-72 (Box 81, Folder 18)
    - All My Sons, 1948 (Box 81, Folder 19)
    - Amahl and the Night Visitors (Box 81, Folder 20)
    - American Dream and Zoo Story, 1962 (Box 81, Folder 21)
    - Among Ourselves, 1956 (Box 81, Folder 22)
    - And Niobe Wept, 1938 (Box 81, Folder 23)
    - Andersonville Trial, 1962 (Box 81, Folder 24)
    - Anna Christie, 1943 (Box 81, Folder 25)
    - Anna Kleiber, 1963 (Box 81, Folder 26)
    - Anniversary Waltz, 1956 (Box 81, Folder 27)
    - Another Part of the Forest, 1948 (Box 81, Folder 28)
    - Antigone, 1965 (Box 81, Folder 29)
    - Anything Goes, 1972 (Box 82, Folder 1)
    - Arms and the Man, 1967 (Box 82, Folder 2)
    - Arsenic and Old Lace, 1951 (Box 82, Folder 3)
    - Arthur and the Magic Sword, 1957 (Box 82, Folder 4)
    - At War with the Army, 1950 (Box 82, Folder 5)
    - Babes in Arms, 1961-62 (Box 82, Folder 6)
    - Barefoot in the Park, 1967 (Box 82, Folder 7)
    - Beauty and the Beast, 1958-1959 (Box 82, Folder 8)
    - Beauty and the Beast, 1961-1962 (Box 82, Folder 9)
    - Beauty and the Beast, 1964-1965 (Box 82, Folder 10)
    - Bernadine, 1958 (Box 82, Folder 11)
    - Between Friends, 1954 (Box 82, Folder 12)
    - Between Two Thieves, 1961 (Box 82, Folder 13)
    - Beyond the Fringe, 1965 (Box 82, Folder 14)
    - Big Fish, Little Fish, 1961 (Box 82, Folder 15)
    - Biography, 1940 (Box 82, Folder 16)
    - The Bishop Misbehaves, 1944 (Box 82, Folder 17)
    - Blind Alley, 1944 (Box 82, Folder 18)
    - Blithe Spirit, 1945 (Box 82, Folder 19)
    - Blithe Spirit, 1971 (Box 82, Folder 20)
    - Blue Denim, 1959 (Box 82, Folder 21)
    - The Blue Fairy, 1982 (Box 82, Folder 22)
    - Born Yesterday, 1967 (Box 82, Folder 23)
    - Both Your Houses, 1946 (Box 82, Folder 24)
    - The Boyfriend, 1957 (Box 82, Folder 25)
    - Boy Meets Girl, 1946 (Box 83, Folder 1)
    - Boys in the Band, 1971 (Box 83, Folder 2)
    - Brave Little Tailor, 1971 (Box 83, Folder 3)
    - Brief Moments [set] (Box 83, Folder 4)
    - Brockett and Barbara Upstairs, 1968-1969 (Box 83, Folder 5)
    - Bus Stop, 1956 (Box 83, Folder 6)
    - Bye Bye Birdie, 1962-1963 (Box 83, Folder 7)
    - Cactus Flower, 1972 (Box 83, Folder 8)
    - Caine Mutiny Court Martial, 1955 (Box 83, Folder 9)
    - Calculated Risk, 1964 (Box 83, Folder 10)
    - Candida, 1944 (Box 83, Folder 11)
    - Canterville Ghost, 1992 (Box 83, Folder 12)
    - Captain Brassbound's Conversion, 1950 (Box 83, Folder 13)
    - Career, 1966 (Box 83, Folder 14)
    - The Caretaker, 1963 (Box 83, Folder 15)
    - Carousel, 1973 (Box 83, Folder 16)
    - Catch Me If You Can, 1971 (Box 83, Folder 17)
    - The Cave Dwellers, 1959 (Box 83, Folder 18)
    - The Chairs and the Bald Soprano (Box 83, Folder 19)
    - Champagne Complex, 1956 (Box 83, Folder 20)
    - Charley's Aunt, 1941-1942 (Box 83, Folder 21)
    - Charley's Aunt, 1974 (Box 83, Folder 22)
    - The Charm Kid, 1950-1951 (Box 83, Folder 23)
    - Cheating at Love, 1960 (Box 83, Folder 24)
    - Children of Darkness, 1935 (Box 84, Folder 1)
    - A Chorus Line (Box 84, Folder 2)
    - A Christmas Carol, 1984 (Box 84, Folder 3)
    - A Christmas Nightingale, 1950 (Box 84, Folder 4)
    - Cinderella (Box 84, Folder 5-6)
    - Cinderella, 1957 (Box 84, Folder 7)
    - Cinderella, 1964-1965 (Box 84, Folder 8)
    - Circus Day, 1953 (Box 84, Folder 9)
    - Come Blow Your Horn, 1963 (Box 84, Folder 10)
    - Command Decision, 1949 (Box 84, Folder 11)
    - The Complaisant Lover, 1966 (Box 84, Folder 12)
    - Coppelia (Box 84, Folder 13)
    - Count Your Blessings, 1943 (Box 84, Folder 14)
    - Crazy Cricket Farm, 1952 (Box 84, Folder 15)
    - The Cradle Song, 1943 (Box 84, Folder 16)
    - Critic's Choice, 1962 (Box 84, Folder 17)
    - The Crucible, 1955 (Box 84, Folder 18)
    - The Curious Savage, 1951 (Box 84, Folder 19)
    - The Damask Cheek, 1945 (Box 84, Folder 20)
    - Dame Nature, 1945 (Box 84, Folder 21)
    - Dames at Sea, 1982 (Box 84, Folder 21a)
    - The Dark at the Top of the Stairs, 1960 (Box 84, Folder 22)
    - The Darkling Plain, 1944 (Box 84, Folder 23)
    - The Deadly Game, 1961 (Box 84, Folder 24)
    - Dear Me! The Sky is Falling, 1969 (Box 84, Folder 25)
    - Death of a Salesman, 1965 (Box 84, Folder 26)
    - Dear Liar, 1983-1984 (Box 84, Folder 27)
    - Death Trap, 1980-1981 (Box 84, Folder 28)
    - Dracula (Box 85, Folder 1)
    - A Delicate Balance, 1968 (Box 85, Folder 2)
    - The Desk Set, 1961 (Box 85, Folder 3)
    - The Desperate Hours, 1956 (Box 85, Folder 4)
    - The Detective Story, 1951 (Box 85, Folder 5)
    - Devil's Disciple, 1965 (Box 85, Folder 6)
    - Dial M for Murder, 1955 (Box 85, Folder 7)
    - Do You Know the Milky Way?, 1964 (Box 85, Folder 8)
    - Doctor In Spite of Himself, 1939 (Box 85, Folder 9)
    - Dots and Dash, 1942 (Box 85, Folder 10)
    - Dream Girl, 1947 (Box 85, Folder 11)
    - Eight Review Sketches, 1969 (Box 85, Folder 12)
    - The Elves and the Shoemaker, 1953 (Box 85, Folder 13)
    - The Elves and the Shoemaker, 1962-1963 (Box 85, Folder 14)
    - The Emperor's New Clothes, 1961 (Box 85, Folder 15)
    - Enter a Free Man, 1972 (Box 85, Folder 16)
    - Enter Laughing, 1964 (Box 85, Folder 17)
    - The Entertainer, 1966-1967 (Box 85, Folder 18)
    - [Unidentified] - in envelope marked The Entertainer (Box 85, Folder 19)
    - Epitaph for George Dillon, 1959-1960 (Box 85, Folder 20)
    - Eve of St. Mark, 1942 (Box 85, Folder 21)
    - Everybody is Wonderful, 1943 (Box 85, Folder 22)
    - Everything in the Garden, 1970 (Box 85, Folder 23)
    - Excursion, 1937 (Box 85, Folder 24)
    - The Fantasticks, 1963 (Box 85, Folder 25)
    - Fashion, 1945-1946 (Box 85, Folder 26)
    - The Fifth Season, 1963 (Box 85, Folder 27)
    - Fifty Grand, 1950 (Box 85, Folder 28)
    - Finian's Rainbow, 1957-1958 (Box 85, Folder 29)
    - The Firebugs, 1965 (Box 86, Folder 1)
    - The First Legion, 1937 (Box 86, Folder 2)
    - First Night, 1963 (Box 86, Folder 3)
    - Flippertygibbet, 1955 (Box 86, Folder 4)
    - Footprints of the Dragon, 1971-1972 (Box 86, Folder 5)
    - Forest Ring, 1951 and/or 1955? (Box 86, Folder 6)
    - Forty Carats, 1970 (Box 86, Folder 7)
    - The Frog Princess, 1961 (Box 86, Folder 8)
    - The Frog Princess and the Witch, 1983 (Box 86, Folder 9)
    - From Morn to Midnight, 1936 (Box 86, Folder 10)
    - Front Page, 1946 (Box 86, Folder 11)
    - Funny Thing Happened on the Way to the Forum, 1965 (Box 86, Folder 12)
    - Galileo, 1968 (Box 86, Folder 13)
    - Gas Light, 1941 (Box 86, Folder 14)
    - The Gazebo, 1960 (Box 86, Folder 15)
    - Generation, 1968 (Box 86, Folder 16)
    - George Washington Slept Here, 1942 (Box 86, Folder 17)
    - Getting Out, 1986-1987 (Box 86, Folder 18)
    - Ghost of Mr. Penny (Box 86, Folder 19)
    - Ghost of Mr. Penny, 1979 (Box 86, Folder 20)
    - The Ghost of Yankee Doodle, 1939 (Box 86, Folder 21)
    - Girl from Wyoming, 1948 (Box 86, Folder 22)
    - Girl on the Via Flaminia, 1955 (Box 86, Folder 23)
    - Glass Menagerie, 1965 (Box 87, Folder 1)
    - Golden Crucible (Box 87, Folder 2)
    - Golden Fleecing (Plus one negative of performance photo), 1960 (Box 87, Folder 3)
    - Goodbye Again, 1943 (Box 87, Folder 4)
    - Goodbye My Fancy, 1950 (Box 87, Folder 5)
    - Grand Guignol, 1950 (Box 87, Folder 6)
    - Great Big Doorstep, 1945 (Box 87, Folder 7)
    - Great Sebastians, 1964 (Box 87, Folder 8)
    - Green Grows the Lilacs, 1942 (Box 87, Folder 9)
    - Green Pastures, 1941 (Box 87, Folder 10)
    - Greensleeve's Magic, 1957 (Box 87, Folder 11)
    - Guys and Dolls, 1971 (Box 87, Folder 12)
    - Gypsy (Box 87, Folder 13)
    - Hamlet, 1961 (Box 87, Folder 14)
    - Hand in Glove, 1945 (Box 87, Folder 15)
    - Hansel and Gretel, 1950 (Box 87, Folder 16)
    - Hansel and Gretel, 1957 (Box 87, Folder 17)
    - Hansel and Gretel, 1963 (Box 87, Folder 18)
    - Hansel and Gretel, 1966-1967 (Box 87, Folder 19)
    - Hansel and Gretel, 1972 (Box 87, Folder 20)
    - Happy Birthday, 1954 (Box 87, Folder 21)
    - The Happy Time, 1952 (Box 87, Folder 22)
    - The Hasty Heart, 1947 (Box 87, Folder 23)
    - Hay Fever (Box 88, Folder 1)
    - Heaven Can Wait, 1944 (Box 88, Folder 2)
    - Henry IV Part I, 1967 (Box 88, Folder 3)
    - Here Today, 1940 (Box 88, Folder 4)
    - History of the American Film, 1979 (Box 88, Folder 5)
    - Hold Your Hats, 1938 (Box 88, Folder 6)
    - A Hole in the Head, 1959 (Box 88, Folder 7)
    - Holiday for Lovers, 1958 (Box 88, Folder 8)
    - Holly and the Ivy, 1952-1953 (Box 88, Folder 9)
    - Home of the Brave, 1954 (Box 88, Folder 10)
    - The Hostage, 1971 (Box 88, Folder 11)
    - How the Other Half Loves, 1972 (Box 88, Folder 12)
    - Hurricane Island, 1955 (Box 88, Folder 13)
    - The Hypochondriac, 1939 (Box 88, Folder 14)
    - I Want a Policeman, 1939 (Box 88, Folder 15)
    - The Importance of Being Earnest, 1949 (Box 88, Folder 16)
    - The Importance of Being Earnest, 1982 (Box 88, Folder 17)
    - In a Garden (Box 88, Folder 18)
    - Inspector General, 1964-1965 (Box 88, Folder 19)
    - Irish Comedy (Box 88, Folder 20)
    - It Can't Happen Here, 1938 (Box 88, Folder 21)
    - Jack and the Beanstalk, 1960 (Box 88, Folder 22)
    - Jack and the Beanstalk, 1964-1965 (Box 88, Folder 23)
    - Jack or the Submission, 1969 (Box 88, Folder 24)
    - Jenny Kissed Me, 1950 (Box 88, Folder 25)
    - The Jest, 1956 (Box 88, Folder 26)
    - Joan of Lorraine, 1948 (Box 88, Folder 27)
    - Joe Egg, 1970 (Box 89, Folder 1)
    - John Loves Mary, 1953 (Box 89, Folder 2)
    - June Moon, 1947-1948 (Box 89, Folder 3)
    - Juno and the Paycock, 1946 (Box 89, Folder 4)
    - The King and I, 1969 (Box 89, Folder 5)
    - King Lear, 1965 (Box 89, Folder 6)
    - King Midas, 1967-1968 (Box 89, Folder 7)
    - King Midas and the Golden Touch, 1954 (Box 89, Folder 8)
    - King of Hearts, 1955 (Box 89, Folder 9)
    - King of the Golden River, 1956 (Box 89, Folder 10)
    - Kiss and Tell, 1946 (Box 89, Folder 11)
    - The Knack, 1966 (Box 89, Folder 12)
    - Lady of Lely Square, 1947 (Box 89, Folder 13)
    - Land of the Dragon, 1949-1950 (Box 89, Folder 14)
    - Last Meeting of the Knight of the White Magnolia, 1980 (Box 89, Folder 15)
    - Last of the Red Hot Lovers, 1972-1973 (Box 89, Folder 16)
    - Late Christopher Bean, 1955 (Box 89, Folder 17)
    - Late George Apley, 1947 (Box 89, Folder 18)
    - Leave It to Jane, 1960 (Box 89, Folder 19)
    - Lend an Ear, 1941 (Box 90, Folder 1)
    - Libel, 1938 (Box 90, Folder 2)
    - Legend of Harlequin, 1960-1961 (Box 90, Folder 3)
    - Life in the Theater, 1980 (Box 90, Folder 4)
    - Life with Mother, 1953 (Box 90, Folder 5)
    - The Lighter Side, 1955 (Box 90, Folder 6)
    - Lion in Winter, 1972 (Box 90, Folder 7)
    - Lion in Winter, 1982 (Box 90, Folder 8)
    - Little Foxes, 1946 (Box 90, Folder 9)
    - Little Foxes, 1968 (Box 90, Folder 10)
    - Little Foxes, 1983 (Box 90, Folder 11)
    - The Little Hut, 1955 (Box 90, Folder 12)
    - Little Mary Sunshine, 1961 (Box 90, Folder 13)
    - The Little Wife, 1953 (Box 90, Folder 14)
    - Little Red Riding Hood, 1953 (Box 90, Folder 15)
    - Lost in the Stars, 1958 (Box 90, Folder 16)
    - Loud Red Patrick, 1957 (Box 90, Folder 17)
    - Love from Judy, 1957 (Box 90, Folder 18)
    - Luv, 1971 (Box 90, Folder 19)
    - The Mad Show, 1966 (Box 91, Folder 1)
    - The Magic Horn, 1958 (Box 91, Folder 2)
    - Make a Million, 1959 (Box 91, Folder 3)
    - Make a Note of It, 1963 (Box 91, Folder 4)
    - The Male Animal, 1941 (Box 91, Folder 5)
    - The Man from Home, 1956 (Box 91, Folder 6)
    - Man in the Dog Suit, 1959 (Box 91, Folder 7)
    - A Man's a Man, 1966 (Box 91, Folder 8)
    - Many Moons, 1958 (Box 91, Folder 9)
    - Marco and the Thieves, 1958 (Box 91, Folder 10)
    - Marriage-go-round, 1961 (Box 91, Folder 11)
    - Mary Mary, 1965 (Box 91, Folder 12)
    - Mary Stuart, 1959 (Box 91, Folder 13)
    - The Matchmaker, 1958 (Box 91, Folder 14)
    - Meet My Sister, 1939 (Box 91, Folder 15)
    - Memory of Two Mondays, 1957 (Box 91, Folder 16)
    - Middle of the Night, 1959 (Box 91, Folder 17)
    - Midsummer Night's Dream, 1960 (Box 91, Folder 18)
    - Mighty Mikko and the Fox, 1959 (Box 91, Folder 19)
    - The Miracle Worker (Point Park College Student Company) (Box 91, Folder 20)
    - Mister Roberts, 1953 (Box 91, Folder 21)
    - Mr. and Mrs. North, 1942 (Box 92, Folder 1)
    - Mrs. Moonlight, 1943 (Box 92, Folder 2)
    - Monique, 1961 (Box 92, Folder 3)
    - Mornings at Seven, 1956 (Box 92, Folder 4)
    - The Mousetrap, 1956 (Box 92, Folder 5)
    - Mr. Ambassador, 1958 (Box 92, Folder 6)
    - Murder Has Been Arranged, 1943 (Box 92, Folder 7)
    - Mutiny in Space, 1980 (Box 92, Folder 8)
    - My Friend the Fox, 1962-1963 (Box 92, Folder 9)
    - My Three Angels, 1954 (Box 92, Folder 10)
    - Mystery at Crooked Pine Ranch, 1969 (Box 92, Folder 11)
    - Mystery of Edwin Drood, 1989 (Box 92, Folder 12)
    - Mystery at the Old Fort, 1969 (Box 92, Folder 13)
    - Mystery of the Forest Ring (Box 92, Folder 14)
    - Mystery of the Ming Tree, 1960 (Box 92, Folder 15)
    - Mysterious Arabian Night, 1960 (Box 92, Folder 16)
    - Mysterious Sandalwood Box, 1956 (Box 92, Folder 17)
    - Naughty Nifties, 1964 (Box 92, Folder 18)
    - Never Too Late, 1972 (Box 92, Folder 19)
    - Night Must Fall - Signed by cast, 1939 (Box 92, Folder 20)
    - Night of January 16, 1943 (Box 92, Folder 21)
    - Nine Girls, 1944 (Box 92, Folder 22)
    - No Strings, 1971 (Box 92, Folder 23)
    - No Time for Sergeants, 1958 (Box 92, Folder 24)
    - Noah, 1965 (Box 92, Folder 25)
    - Nude with Violin, 1961 (Box 93, Folder 1)
    - Odd Couple, 1968 (Box 93, Folder 2)
    - Of All Things, 1949 (Box 93, Folder 3)
    - Of Mice and Men, 1954 (Box 93, Folder 4)
    - Off the Top, 1957 (Box 93, Folder 5)
    - Oh Dad Poor Dad, 1964 (Box 93, Folder 6)
    - Oh Kay!, 1962 (Box 93, Folder 7)
    - Oh Men! Oh Women!, 1955-1956 (Box 93, Folder 8)
    - Old Acquaintance, 1943 (Box 93, Folder 9)
    - On Borrowed Time, 1944 (Box 93, Folder 10)
    - On the Spot, 1936 (Box 93, Folder 11)
    - On Your Mark, 1951 (Box 93, Folder 12)
    - Once More With Feeling, 1959 (Box 93, Folder 13)
    - Once Upon a Mattress, 1967 (Box 93, Folder 14)
    - Once Upon a Mattress, 1982 (Box 93, Folder 15)
    - Open Season, 1960 (Box 93, Folder 16)
    - Our Town, 1955 (Box 93, Folder 17)
    - Out of the Frying Pan, 1941 (Box 93, Folder 18)
    - Owl and the Pussycat, 1969 (Box 93, Folder 19)
    - A Pair of Spectacles, 1962 (Box 93, Folder 20)
    - The Panda and the Spy, 1951 (Box 93, Folder 21)
    - Papa is All, 1944 (Box 94, Folder 1)
    - Papa Pompino and the Prizefighter, 1955 (Box 94, Folder 2)
    - A Party, 1945 (Box 94, Folder 3)
    - Payment Deferred, 1953 (Box 94, Folder 4)
    - Peg O' My Heart, 1952 (Box 94, Folder 5)
    - Penny Wise, 1943 (Box 94, Folder 6)
    - Period of Adjustment, 1961 (Box 94, Folder 7)
    - Personal Appearance, 1938-1939 (Box 94, Folder 8)
    - Petticoat Fever, 1944 (Box 94, Folder 9)
    - Pictures in the Hallway, 1961 (Box 94, Folder 10)
    - Pinocchio, 1965 (Box 94, Folder 11)
    - Pinocchio, 1958-1959 (Box 94, Folder 12)
    - Play It Again Sam, 1972 (Box 94, Folder 13)
    - The Play's the Thing, 1944 (Box 94, Folder 14)
    - Playboy of the Western World, 1962 (Box 94, Folder 15)
    - Playhouse Follies, 1965 (Box 94, Folder 16)
    - Plaza Suite, 1971 (Box 94, Folder 17)
    - Pied Piper of Hamlin, 1954 (Box 94, Folder 18)
    - Pied Piper of Hamlin, 1962 (Box 94, Folder 19)
    - Pied Piper of Hamlin, 1966-1967 (Box 94, Folder 20)
    - Pleasure of His Company, 1962 (Box 94, Folder 21)
    - Poor Nut, 1946-1947 (Box 94, Folder 22)
    - Post Road, 1943 (Box 94, Folder 23)
    - Potting Shed, 1957 (Box 94, Folder 24)
    - Present Laughter, 1951-1952 (Box 95, Folder 1)
    - Prime of Miss Jean Brodie, 1973 (Box 95, Folder 2)
    - Princeton Triangle Club-Future Schlock, 1973 (Box 95, Folder 3)
    - The Prisoner, 1961 (Box 95, Folder 4)
    - Private Ear and Public Eye, 1965 (Box 95, Folder 5)
    - Private Lives, 1939 (Box 95, Folder 6)
    - Pursuit of Happiness, 1937 (Box 95, Folder 7)
    - Puss in Boots, 1956 (Box 95, Folder 8)
    - Pygmalion, 1954 (Box 95, Folder 9)
    - The Queen's Husband, 1954 (Box 95, Folder 10)
    - Rapunzel and the Witch, 1973 (Box 95, Folder 11)
    - Rapunzel and the Witch, 1982 (Box 95, Folder 12)
    - Reclining Figure, 1955 (Box 95, Folder 13)
    - Reflected Glory, 1940-1941 (Box 95, Folder 14)
    - Remains to be Seen, 1952 (Box 95, Folder 15)
    - Remarkable Mr. Pennypacker, 1955 (Box 95, Folder 16)
    - Remember Me, 1949 (Box 95, Folder 17)
    - Rhinoceros, 1966 (Box 95, Folder 18)
    - The Road to Rome, 1940 (Box 95, Folder 19)
    - Roar Like a Dove, 1961 (Box 95, Folder 20)
    - Robber Bridegroom, 1981 (Box 95, Folder 21)
    - Robinson Crusoe, 1965-1966 (Box 95, Folder 22)
    - Robin Hood (Box 95, Folder 23)
    - Robin Hood, 1952 (Box 96, Folder 1)
    - Robin Hood, 1982 (Box 96, Folder 2)
    - Romanoff and Juliet, 1960 (Box 96, Folder 3)
    - Room Service, 1970 (Box 96, Folder 4)
    - Roomful of Roses, 1956 (Box 96, Folder 5)
    - Rope Dancers, 1959 (Box 96, Folder 6)
    - Rose Tattoo, 1965 (Box 96, Folder 7)
    - The Royal Family, 1953 (Box 96, Folder 8)
    - The Royal Gambit, 1980-1981 (Box 96, Folder 9)
    - Rumpelstiltskin, 1959 (Box 96, Folder 10)
    - Rumpelstiltskin, 1964 (Box 96, Folder 11)
    - Rumpelstiltskin, 1969 (Box 96, Folder 12)
    - Russet Mantle, 1938 (Box 96, Folder 13)
    - Sabrina Fair, 1954-1955 (Box 96, Folder 14)
    - Sailor Beware, 1960 (Box 96, Folder 15)
    - Scarlet Letter, 1936 (Box 96, Folder 16)
    - Secret Garden, 1992 (Box 96, Folder 17)